Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 90th Congress, 1962-1968; Undated; 6; 12.4 cubic ft.
  - Peace Corps, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Peace Office and Civil Service Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Peace Office Department, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Postal Employees Raise (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Postal Employees Raise (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Postal Workers, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Prayer Amendment, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Problems of Aging, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Q" Last Names, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "R" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Labor Dispute, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Redwood National Park (California), 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Representative Powell Investigation, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "S" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Select Committee on Small Business, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Service Academies -[RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Social Security, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Social Security Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Social Security Petition Letter, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Background Material on the Kennedy Round (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Background Material on the Kennedy Round (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Congressman Tunney's Resolution H. Con. 815, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Correspondence on U.S. Investment, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Hearings and Reports on Private Investment, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Hearings on Kennedy Round, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Press Coverage on Hearings Held on U.S. Investment, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy: Questionnaires on Private Investment, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "T" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tax Increases (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Tax Increases (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Transportation Department, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Travel Restrictions (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Travel Restrictions (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Travel Restrictions with Suggested Exemptions, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Treasury Department, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Truth-in-Lending, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "U" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Un-American Activities Committees, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - United States Information Agency, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - "V" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Veterans' Affairs Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "W" Last Names, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - West Point -[RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - West Point Academic Year 1968-1969 -[RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - West Point Academy: Michael T. Glynne (Graduated June 1965), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "X"-"Z" Last Names, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- The 91st Congress, 1963-1970; Undated; 7; 11.2 cubic ft.
  The records found in this series consist of legislative actions, correspondence with constituents, newspaper clippings, and subject-specific documents. Such subjects fall under the categories of: Foreign Affairs and various Departments and Committees. The Food Stamps Program documentation is also found within this series. Within this series are also applications to military academies to be approved by Farbstein. As these materials contain personally identifiable information, these specific files have been restricted.
  - Agency for International Development, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Air Force, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annapolis -[RESTRICTED], 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Energy Speech City Council of New York, 1970-03-04 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Banking and Currency Commission, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bureau of the Census, 1967-1968; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Youth Council: VISTA Application, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Coast Guard, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Customs Bureau, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Ad Hoc Hearing on Air Pollution, 1969-10-28 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Air Pollution Amendments, 1970-06-04 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Air Pollution Legislation, 1970-04-05 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Amendment to Abolish the Draft, 1969-10-22 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Amendment to Clean Air Act, 1969-09-04 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Biafra Resolution, 1969-08-05 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Dealing with Live Ammunition by National Guardsmen on College Campuses, 1970-05-13 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Draft Repeal Resolution with Crane, 1970-03-05 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Justice Department Anti-Trust Air Pollution Suit Against Big Four Auto Companies, 1969-09-26 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Food Coding Bill, 1970-04-09 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Mayor Lindsay on Air Pollution Anti-Trust Suit, 1969-09-16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Middle East Special Order, 1970-02-23 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Middle East Vigil Before Pompidou Visit, 1970-02-11 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dear Colleague Letter on Steam Engine Demonstration, 1970-03-24 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dear Colleague Letter Regarding the Dating of Perishable and Semi-Perishable Foods on Grocery Shelves, 1970-02-11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Dear Colleague Letter Regarding Letter Sent to Hon. Daniel Flood to Restore Cuts to Federal Aid to Education and Aid to Libraries, 1969-07-14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Department of the Army, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Department of the Army: Complaint to West Point from the Hudson Guild, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Department of the Army: Mutiny Trials at San Francisco Presidio Stockade, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Department of Commerce, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Department of Commerce: Mobilization for Youth, Inc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Department of the Interior, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Department of Justice, 1967; 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Department of Labor, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Department of the Navy, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Economic Development Administration Amendments, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Economic Development Administration Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Economic Development Administration: Mobilization for Youth, Inc., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - EDA Amendment: H.R. 9832, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program: Bid from OEO for Comprehensive Study of Program, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program: Community Corporation of the Lower West Side, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. and Project Proposal Sioux Buying Club Rosebud Reservation, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Emergency Small Loan Program Summary, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Emco Porcelain and Enamel Company, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, 1968; 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Federal Housing Administration, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Food and Drug Administration: Food Stamp Program (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Food and Drug Administration: Food Stamp Program (2 of 2), 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Food and Drug Administration: Thompson Medical Company, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Food Stamp Program, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Food Stamp Program, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Food Stamp Program Correspondence (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Food Stamp Program Correspondence (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Food Stamp Program Information, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Food Stamp Program Statements, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Anti-Semitism, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugees, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Biafra, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Affairs: Committee on Foreign Affairs (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Affairs: Committee on Foreign Affairs (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee: American Congress for Irish Freedom, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee: Illegal Drug Traffic, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Affairs: Egypt, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Affairs: Europe, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel Pompidou Visit, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs: Laos, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East Refugees, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Affairs: Near East Report, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Affairs: Subcommittee on Foreign Economic Policy, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Aid Bill, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Aid Bill: Weizman and Hadassah Amendments, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1966; 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - General Services Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - H. Con. Res. 78: A Concurrent Resolution Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to Prosecutions for War Crimes in the Federal Republic of Germany (Includes Other Bills), 1965; 1967; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - H. Con. Res. 144: A Concurrent Resolution of Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to Reduced Air Fairs for Children, Youth, and Members of the Armed Forces of the United States, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - H. Con. Res. 186: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress that the United States Should Begin to Reduce Its Military Involvement in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - H. Con. Res. 201: A Concurrent Resolution to Print Additional Copies of the Memorial Tributes Delivered in Congress on the Late Senator Robert Francis Kennedy, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - H. Con. Res. 256: A Concurrent Resolution for the Sense of Congress that the President Should Direct an Immediate Unconditional Withdrawal of One Hundred Thousand United States Troops from Vietnam, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - H. Con. Res. 259: A Concurrent Resolution on Urgency of Arms Control Negotiation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - H. Con. Res. 283: A Concurrent Resolution Relating to an Atlantic Union Delegation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - H. Con. Res. 312: A Concurrent Resolution to Invite Members of the Supreme Soviet to Visit the United States, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - H. Con. Res. 314: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress Relating to Films and Broadcasts Which Defame, Stereotype, Ridicule, Demean or Degrade Ethnic, Racial and Religious Groups, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - H. Con. Res. 405: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress that the Federal Power Commission Should Render a Decision in the Matter of the Application in Project Numbered 23-38, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - H. Con. Res. 416: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress with Respect to the Assignment to Vietnam of Persons Inducted into the Armed Forces, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - H. Con. Res. 424: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to the Establishment of United Nations Day as a Permanent International Holiday, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - H. Con. Res. 432: A Concurrent Resolution to Provide that Executive Departments, Agencies, or Instrumentalities of the Federal Government Respond Within Sixty Days to Requests from Committees of Congress, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - H. Con. Res. 461: A Concurrent Resolution Condemning Syria for Illegally Detaining Two Israeli Citizens Who Were Passengers Aboard a Trans World Airlines Aircraft Hijacked by Air Pirates on August 29, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - H. Con. Res. 463: A Concurrent Resolution to Express the Sense of the Congress that the President of the United States Should Take Prompt and Effective Action to Correct All Inequalities in the Case of A.E. Fitzgerald, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - H. Con. Res. 479: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the House with Respect to Peace in the Middle East, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - H. Con. Res. 511: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress that the United States Should Sell Israel Aircraft Necessary for Israel's Defense, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - H. Con. Res. 519: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress Concerning the Use of Certain Real Property in New York City for Low- and Moderate-Income Housing, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - H. Con. Res. 531: A Concurrent Resolution to Establish a Joint Congressional Committee on Foreign Policy, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - H. Con. Res. 533: A Concurrent Resolution Urging the President to Determine and Undertake Appropriate Actions with Respect to Stopping Armed Attacks on Aircraft and Prisoners Engaged in International Travel, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - H. Con. Res. 543: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to the Establishment of All-Volunteer Armed Forces (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - H. Con. Res. 543: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress with Respect to the Establishment of All-Volunteer Armed Forces (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - H. Con. Res. 544: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress with Respect to the Establishment of All-Volunteer Armed Forces, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - H. Con. Res. 556: A Concurrent Resolution on the Middle East, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - H. Con. Res. 563: A Concurrent Resolution for Condemning Soviet Treatment of Its Jewish Population, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - H. Con. Res. 593: A Concurrent Resolution for State of the Federal Judiciary Address, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - H. Con. Res. 602: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the Congress Regarding Further Steps of the President Concerning Cambodia, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - H. Con. Res. 616: A Concurrent Resolution for Providing a Joint Session of Congress on Friday May 22, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - H. Con. Res. 684: A Concurrent Resolution for Relating to Treatment and Exchange of Military and Civilian Prisoners in Vietnam, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - H. Con. Res. 719: A Concurrent Resolution for Expressing the Sense of Congress that the President Should Instruct the American Delegation to the Diplomatic Conference to Revise the Warsaw Convention, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - H. Con. Res. 744: A Concurrent Resolution Regarding Persecution of Jews in Russia, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - H. Con. Res. 780: A Concurrent Resolution Urging Review of the United Nations Charter, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - H. J. Res. 54: A Joint Resolution Proposing an Amendment to the Constitution of the United States Relating to the Conservation of the Natural Resources and Natural Beauty of the United, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - H. J. Res. 229: A Joint Resolution Proposing an Amendment to the Constitution of the United States Relative to Equal Rights for Men and Women (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963; 1965-1966; 1967 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - H. J. Res. 230: A Joint Resolution to Authorize to Designate October 31 of Each as Year "National UNICEF Day" (Also Contains Related Bills), 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - H. J. Res. 231: A Joint Resolution Designating the 14th Day of March of Each Year as Albert Einstein Memorial Day (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963; 1967; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - H. J. Res. 232: A Joint Resolution for Proposing an Amendment to the Constitution of the United States Providing that the Term of Office of Members of the United States House of Representative Shall be Four Years, 1965; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - H. J. Res. 234: A Joint Resolution Designating January 15 of Each Year as "Martin Luther King Day" (Also Contains Related Bills), 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - H. J. Res. 233: A Joint Resolution Designating the Fourth Sunday in September of Each Year as "Interfaith Day", 1969 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - H. J. Res. 235: A Joint Resolution Designating July 25 of Each Year as "Puerto Rican Day in the United States of America" (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - H. J. Res. 252: A Joint Resolution to Direct the Federal Communications Commission to Conduct a Comprehensive Study and Investigation of the Effects of the Display of Violence in Television Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - H. J. Res. 381: A Joint Resolution Consenting to the Susquehanna River Basin Compact, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - H. J. Res. 482: A Joint Resolution to Consent to and Enter Into the Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - H. J. Res. 683: A Joint Resolution to Direct the Federal Communications Commission to Study the Ways in Which Commercial Broadcasters May be Required to Provide Financial Support to Nonprofit Public Educational Broadcasters, 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - H. J. Res. 930: A Joint Resolution to Supplement the Joint Resolution Making Continuing Appropriations for the Fiscal Year 1970 in Order to Provide for Carrying Out Programs and Projects, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - H. J. Res. 953: A Joint Resolution to Establish a Joint Commission of the United States, The Republic of South Vietnam and the International Commission for Supervision and Control in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - H. J. Res. 983: A Joint Resolution to Provide a Program to Improve the Opportunity of Students in Elementary and Secondary Schools to Study Cultural Heritages of Major Ethnic Groups in the Nation, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - H. J. Res. 1103: A Joint Resolution to Repeal Legislation Relating to the Use of the Armed Forces of the United States in Southeast Asia, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - H. J. Res. 1203: A Joint Resolution Designating the Third Wednesday of April of Each Year as "Earth Day", 1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 165: A Bill for Amendment of the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 301: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Merchant Marine Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 745: A Bill to Provide for the Designation of the Veterans' Administration Hospital in Jackson, Mississippi as the "Medgar Evers Memorial Hospital" (Also Contains H. R. 15270), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 2653: A Bill for Amendment of Title 10 of the United States Code, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 2654: A Bill for Amendment of Section 213 of the National Housing Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1964; 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 2655: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 2656: A Bill to Establish a Federal Motor Vehicle Insurance Guaranty Corporation, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - H. R. 2657: A Bill for Amendment of Chapter 115 of Title 28 United States Code (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965; 1967; 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 2658: A Bill for Amendment of the Bankruptcy Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 2659: A Bill to Provide Time off Duty for Government Employees to Comply with Religious Obligations Prescribed by Religious Denominations, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 2660: A Bill to Provide that Arrests of Persons Engaged in Peaceful Activities in Furtherance of Their Rights Shall Not be a Bar to Their Employment by the Federal Government (Also Contains Related Bills), 1965; 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 2661: A Bill to Permit a State to Elect to Use Funds from the Highway Trust Fund for Purposes of Urban Mass Transportation, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 2662: A Bill for Amendment of title 38 of the United States Code (Also Contains H. R. 8607), 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 2663: A Bill to Provide that the Nuclear Accelerator to be Constructed at Weston, Illinois Shall be Named the "Enrico Fermi Nuclear Accelerator" (Also Contains Related Bills), 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 2757: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Also Contains H. R. 14529), 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 2758: A Bill for Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Also Contains H. R. 13245), 1966; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 3084: A Bill for Amendment of Title 7 of the Housing Act of 1961, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 3085: A Bill for Amendment of Section 203(a)(7) of the Immigration and Nationality Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 3086: A Bill for Amendment of Section 114 of Title 18 of the United States Code (Also Contains H. R. 15489), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 3087: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Employees Health Benefits Act of 1959 (Also Contains H. R. 16556), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 3088: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 16516), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 3295: A Bill to Provide for the Establishment of a Commission on Afro-American History and Culture, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 3338: A Bill to Assure to Every American a Full Opportunity to Have Adequate Employment, Housing and Education Free from Any Discrimination, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 3663: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Hazardous Substances Labeling Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 3665: A Bill for Amendment of the Program of Health Insurance Benefits Under Title 18 of the Social Security Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 4190: A Bill to Provide Federal Assistance to Improve the Educational Services in Public and Private Nonprofit Child Day Care Centers, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 4227: A Bill to Provide Educational Assistance to children of Civilian Employees of the United States Killed Abroad as a Result of War, Insurgency or Mob Violence, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 4308: A Bill to Authorize Assistance Under the FHA Section 236 Program and the Rent Supplement Program, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 4793: A Bill to Enable Citizens of the United States Who Change Their Residences to Vote in Presidential Elections, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 5169: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Cigarette Labeling and Advertising Act (Also Contains H. R. 12054), 1967; 1969 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 5202: A Bill for Amendment of Title 4 of the Public Health Service Act, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)